(Sheldon:)- Where do you stand on it?
- Strongly pro.
(Leonard:)Then I believe that God
created the world in six days...
(Leonard:)...and on the seventh
he made you to annoy me.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
(Sheldon:)Raj, where do you stand
on the anthropic principle?
- I'm all for it.
- Thattaboy.
(Leonard:)Why do you believe that he knows
what it is, and I don't?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard...
(Sheldon:)...let's not take a saw to the branch
we're sitting on, shall we?
Hey, if you guys are free tonight
I heard about a spa...
(Raj:)...where you soak your feet
in a pool of fish...
...that eat the dead skin off them.
(Raj:)I don't need to tell you, in Los Angeles...
(Raj:)...sandal season is year round.
- Actually, I'm hanging out with Penny.
- Oh, okay.
(Raj:)Sounds like it's me and you.
(Raj:)How about we sic some guppies
on those puppies?
(Sheldon:)As I've stated before
on numerous occasions...
(Sheldon:)...the only sea creature
I would consider being eaten by...
(Sheldon:)...is the Kraken. Because the last words
I would hear are "release the Kraken."